"I'll never understand that boy.
"But then again,
I'm a religious nut,
(Sheldon:)and my mind is closed
to so many things."
"Spock to Enterprise.
Transport successful."
"Glory be to Heaven,
"some sort of creature
just manifested out of thin air.
"George, put down that Pepsi can
full of bourbon
(Sheldon:)that ain't foolin' no one,
and get your shotgun!"
"Greetings, Mary Cooper.
I am Spock."
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
I just don't buy it.
(Penny:)Just keep going!
"Oh, my, your sudden appearance
startles me."
"We have been monitoring
your son Sheldon
"from the 23rd Century, and
"we have determined
that he is now ready
"to join us.
"His unique genius
is our best hope
(Penny:)for bringing peace
to a vast and troubled galaxy."
"I understand.